A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- Desert Research Institute. "Yucca Mountain program summary of research, site monitoring and technical review activities (January 1987-June 1988." (Box 251, Folder 4)
- Desert Research Institute. "Yucca Mountain program summary of research and technical review activities (October 1990-September 1991." (Box 251, Folder 5)
- Flynn, J. et al. "Time to rethink nuclear waste storage." From Issues in Science and Technology. (Box 251, Folder 6)
- Ho, C-H. "Time trend analysis of basaltic volcanism near the yucca mountain site." (Box 251, Folder 7)
- Justus, P. "Probability of vulcanism at Yucca Mountain." U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. (Box 251, Folder 8)
- Langer, M. "Current status of geotechnical research on the long-term safety of permanent repositories for nuclear waste." From BGR Circular. (Box 251, Folder 9)
- Lappin, A.R. et al. "Thermal conductivity, bulk properties, and thermal stratigraphy of silicic tuffs from the upper portion of hole USW-G1, Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada." (Box 251, Folder 10)
- Linehan, J.J. "[Letter from J.J. Linehan to D.E. Shelor, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management]." (Box 251, Folder 11)
- Knauss, K.G., Oversby, V.M. and Wolery, T.J. "Post emplacement environment of waste packages." (Box 251, Folder 12)
- Missouri Department of Natural Resources. "Geologic investigations at Weldon Spring." From Outlook. (Box 251, Folder 13)
- National Nuclear Security Administration. "Nevada Test Site environmental impact statement supplement analysis [presentation]." (Box 251, Folder 14)
- Nevada Agency for Nuclear Projects Nuclear Waste Project Office. "Spring 1993 Nevada state telephone survey: Key findings." (Box 251, Folder 15)
- Northwest Interstate Compact on Low-Level Radioactive Waste Management. "Northwest interstate compact meetings." (Box 251, Folder 16)
- Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Selected NRC products: High-level waste program." (Box 251, Folder 17)
- Nuclear Waste Project Office. "Nevada's concerns about Yucca Mountain.", undated (Box 251, Folder 18)
- "Review criteria, findings, and recommendations of the review panel.", undated (Box 251, Folder 19)
- Smyth, J.R. "Physical and chemical properties of zeolite minerals occurring at the Yucca Mountain Site." (Box 251, Folder 20)
- State of Nevada. "Summary of technical concerns about site suitability of Yucca Mountain as presented by State of Nevada to Advisory Committee on Nuclear Waste in Washington, D.C. 2/23/89." (Box 251, Folder 21)
- State of Nevada Agency for Nuclear Projects. "Nevada's technical concerns with the proposed nuclear waste repository at Yucca Mountain." (Box 251, Folder 22)
- "Technical position on tectonic models in the assessment of performance of high-level radioactive waste repositories.", undated (Box 251, Folder 23)
- Tennessee Department of Conservation. "Notice of publication of research findings." (Box 251, Folder 24)
- United States Council for Energy Awareness. "U.S. public opinion bulletins." (Box 251, Folder 25)
- United States Nuclear Waste Technical Review Board. "News bulletins." (Box 251, Folder 26)
- United States of America Federal Energy Regulatory Commission. "Public notices." (Box 251, Folder 27)
- United States Department of Energy Nevada Operations Office. "News bulletin." (Box 251, Folder 28)
- United States Department of Energy Office of Environmental Management. "EM Update." (Box 251, Folder 29)
- United States Department of Energy Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Office. "Yucca Mountain Site characterization project update meetings." (Box 251, Folder 30)
- United States Department of the Interior Bureau of Mines. "A computer program for detecting or predicting fracture zones." From Technology News. (Box 251, Folder 31)
- United States Department of the Interior Bureau of Mines. "U.S. Bureau of Mines news." (Box 251, Folder 32)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Nevada Operations Office/Yucca Mountain Project Office. "Preliminary rail access study." (Box 252, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Nevada potential repository preliminary transportation strategy, study 1." B00000000-01717-4600-000023 REV 01. (Box 252, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Nevada potential repository preliminary transportation strategy, study 2." B00000000-01717-4600-000050 REV 01. Vol. I. (Box 252, Folder 3)
- Bechtel SAIC Company LLC. "Mina rail route fesibility study." Rev. 01. (Box 252, Folder 4)
- "Operational safety plan Project Shoal: May, 1963." (Box 253, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Nuclear Waste Policy Act of 1982: General guidelines for the recommendation of sites for the Nuclear Waste Repositories - Supplementary information." (Box 253, Folder 2)
- Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC comments on DOE draft environmental assessment for the Yucca Mountain Site, March 20, 1985." (Box 253, Folder 3)
- Nevada Nuclear Waste Storage Investigations. "NNWSI draft environmental assessment references." (Box 253, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "DOE news: Department of Energy issues mission plan for Civilian Radioactive Waste Program." (Box 253, Folder 5)
- U. S. General Accounting Office. "Statement of Keith O. Fultz Associate Director Resources, Community, and Economic Development Division before the subcommittee on energy and the environment house committee on interior and insular affaris." (Box 253, Folder 6)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "General information on the Yucca Mountain Project." (Box 253, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "DOE technical program review: Design." (Box 253, Folder 8)
- Hardin, E. L. and Chesnut, D. A. "Synthesis report on thermally driven coupled processes [CD-rom]." Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory., undated (Box 253, Folder 9)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Supplement to the final environmental impact statement for a geologic repository for the disposal of spent nuclear fuel and high-level radioactive waste at Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada: Notice of intent.", undated (Box 253, Folder 10)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Amended notice of intent to expand the scope of the final environmental impact statement for the alignment, construction, and operation of a rail line to a geologic repository at Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada.", undated (Box 253, Folder 11)
- Nevada Nuclear Waste Storage Investigations. "Discussion of Yucca Mountain environmental assessment: Introduction.", undated (Box 253, Folder 12)
- Nevada Nuclear Waste Storage Investigations. "Discussion of Yucca Mountain environmental assessment: Overview.", undated (Box 253, Folder 13)
- Nevada Nuclear Waste Storage Investigations. "Discussion of Yucca Mountain environmental assessment.", undated (Box 253, Folder 14)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "DOE/NV listing of DOE standardization documents available in the DOE/NV technical information resource center.", undated (Box 253, Folder 15)
- "Final general guidelines for the recommendation of sites for the Nuclear Waste Reporitories.", undated (Box 253, Folder 16)
- Carlos, B., Bish, D., and Chipera, S. "Fracture-lining minerals in the lower Topopah Spring Tuff at Yucca Mountain." Submitted to Radioactive Waste Management., undated (Box 253, Folder 17)
- Bish, D. L. and Vaniman, D. T. "Mineralogic summary of Yucca Mountain, Nevada.", undated (Box 253, Folder 18)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Public reading room information on the U.S. Department of Energy Nevada Test Site: Environmental impact statement." (Box 254, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Public comments on the U.S. Department of Energy Nevada Test Site: Environmental impact statement." (Box 254, Folder 2)
- Environmental Protection Agency. "Fact Sheet - Yucca Mountain: EPA's proposed public health & environmental standards." (Box 254, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management: Yucca Mountain Project factsheets, tour map, test site map, and spent fuel card." (Box 254, Folder 4)
- Roy, W.R., Mravik, S.C., Krapac, I.G. et al. "Geochemical interactions of hazardous wastes with geological formations in deep-well systems." Department of Energy and Natural Resources, Illinois State Geological Survey. (Box 254, Folder 5)
- "Maps related to the Hanford Site in Washington State." (Box 255, Folder 1)
- "Maps related to Yucca Mountain, Nevada." (Box 256, Folder 1)